

Hau Zheng Yi Frontend Developer

www.hauzhengyi.github.io in www.linkedin.com/in/zyhau

hauzhengyi@hotmail.com

**** +6016673158

Yuala Lumpur, Malaysia

PROFILE

A hard-working developer with good attention to detail, who holds himself to high standards in writing quality codes. Experienced in both various programming languages such as HTML/CSS, JavaScript, PHP, ¡Query, Bootstrap, React, MySQL etc. Communicates well with customers and team members (Mandarin/English), able to learn technologies quickly with minimal guidance. Xiamen University Malaysia Hackathon award winner.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TDCX (MY) Sdn Bhd, Fontend Developer (Project 305)

May 2022 - present Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- · Creating, deploying and troubleshooting implementations such as Google Ads conversion tracking, Google Analytics, Google Merchant Center Shopping Feed, Dynamic Remarketing, Ecommerce Tracking, Google Tag Manager, etc. using CMS platforms such as Wordpress, Shopify, Go Daddy, Squarespace and Wix.
- Helping sales teams deploy leads, implement tags, optimize ads performance, enable integration and troubleshoot customer's issues regarding their online ad campaigns.
- Maintaining clear, concise, and positive communication for all cases in a timely and efficient manner including follow-ups with customers, team members, and engineers.

CUSTLR SaratiX, Web Developer Internship

Feb 2022 - May 2022

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- · Assisted in developing a Shopify webapp with minimal supervision.
- Transforming UI/UX designs into beautiful, responsive web pages.
- · Developed robust backend for e-commerce analytics.
- Skills involved: HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript, Laravel, Bootstrap, jQuery, Ajax, REST API, MySQL.

Sunline Technology (Malaysia) Sdn Bhd, Software Developer Internship

Sep 2021 – Jan 2022 Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Implemented application modules under the direction of Senior Developers using in-house custom Java development software.
- Maintaining and updating large database systems using MySQL.
- Making changes using Git, solving issues when merge conflict occurs.
- Troubleshooting banking software issues, managed cases on JIRA system.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science and Technology,

Aug 2019 - Feb 2022

Sepang, Malaysia

Xiamen University Malaysia

- CGPA 3.55 | XMUM Merit Scholarship | Chinese Ambassador Scholarship
- XMUM Hackathon 2021 Topic 1 Winner: Environmental Issues due to Development of Cities
- Swimming Club Event Planner & Trainer, 2 times Silver Medalist, 3 times Bronze Medalist

® SKILLS

HTML5/CSS3 | JavaScript | React JS | jQuery | Bootstrap 5 | PHP | Laravel | MySQL | C/C++

(A) LANGUAGES

English Chinese

Hau Zheng Yi hauzhengyi@hotmail.com